# Arsenii Ashukha

Moscow, Russia • ⋈ ars.ashuha@gmail.com • ars-ashuha.ru • 23 years old ☺



## Summary

I am a second year Master Student at MIPT also I do research at Bayes Group under supervision of prof. Dmitry Vetrov. My research is focused on Bayesian regularization of deep neural nets. At MIPT, MSU, HSE I teach several Machine Learning courses. To see the publication list visit my scholar profile.

Skills: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Bayesian ML, Python, Hadoop, Linux, Fluent English

#### Education

2015 - 2017	Master, Machine Learning, Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, GPA: 9.0/10.0
Thesis	Variational Dropout Sparsifies DNNs, Supervisor: Prof. D. Vetrov (HSE), A. Dral (MIPT)



2015 - 2016 Irregular Student, Machine Learning, Yandex School of Data Analysis, GPA: 4.8/5.0
Result Six courses were passed and the favorites are Bayesian ML, Deep Learning, Machine Learning



2011 - 2015 Bachelor, Computer Science, Bauman Moscow State Technical University, GPA: 3.7/5.0 Thesis Building of Uncorrelated Kernels for Topic Models, Supervisor: N. Loukachevitch (MSU)



#### Experience

Apr 2017 - Now	HSE, Moscow — Intern Researcher at Lab of DL and Bayesian ML - Research on efficient training of DNNs all details are hidden under NDA Chief: Dmitriy Vetrov (vetrovd@yandex.ru)	HIGHER SCHOOL OF ECONOM
Jun 2016 - Aug 2016 3 month	Yandex, Moscow — Intern at Music Deep Learning Group - Searching similar tracks and building recommendation features using DNN Chief: Eugene Krofto (singleton@yandex-team.ru)	<b>Y</b> andex
Dec 2013 - Feb 2016 2 year 1 month $p/t$	Rambler, Moscow — R&D Engineer at Machine Learning Group  - Improving the quality and performance of user classification using browser history  - Recommendations system for the news posts on rambler.ru  Chief: Pavel Klemenkov (pklemenkov@gmail.com), Anton Gorokhov (anton.gorokhov@gmail.com)	RAMBLER&Co
<b>Jun 2013 - Aug 2013</b> 3 month	Rambler, Moscow — Intern at Search Group  - Users query classification to show a mixing in search results  Chief: Max Karpenko (v3dmax@gmail.com)	RAMBLER&Co

### Teaching

- Feb 2016 Feb 2017: Practical Lecturer of Machine Learning course at MIPT (parts 1,2)
- Sep 2016 Now: Lecturer of several classes of Deep Learning courses at MSU and HSE
- Oct 2016 Now: Lecturer of DL part of Data Mining in Action course, YouTube records in Russian 3
- Feb 2017 Now: Lecturer of DL part in Machine Learning course at MIPT
- Feb 2017 Now: Co-head of Scientific Machine Learning seminar for MIPT and HSE Yandex students